The root of recovery was seen in the market on June 20,
so let us know on
which two stocks the dealers have made claims for earning.
Nifty Little Bag Tip T 200 points, yes,
Nifty Mid Captain
Chadha
saw a rise in the middle beginning after the seventh consecutive nut,
Jindal Steel and Hind Copper were seen trading higher than two days ago, on the
other hand,
IT and Auto saw good buying in the beginning,
Tata Motors reached a 7-year peak,
here Block SDMC Make's share
became the top gainer by cheating and promising more than Art Fiji, on
June 20, in this market environment, let us tell you in
which two strokes the dealers have played in the dealing room,
we have advised the strategy of buy today and sell tomorrow,
so if you have bought the stock today, then
according to that, a rise of 3 to 4%
is possible in this share, buying has been seen from mutual funds in this city,
analysts are looking bullish on the stock, on
June 20, dealers have made claims on private sector insurance
stocks for good earnings,
dears have put their  The client has been advised to
buy shares of ICC Lombard,
but according to it, it is possible to take a
position of even five pieces in this stock. However,
no buying has been seen from its side in the city.
Information is obtained from the dealing room of the brokerage house through sources as to
which two stocks the brokerage advises its
clients to trade the most today, in
which cities they bought and sold and
what is the top trading history of today.
[Music] Do you know
madam, we are going to talk about Britannia, the favourite of every household.
You might
generally think of it as a biscuit company, but
Britannia is not just a biscuit company,
but
you can see this company as a very big food joint in the confectionery business.
This company was started 130 years
ago and was once launched at Rs 245.
It started in a small house in Central Kolkata and from there it gradually
expanded to such a big scale that you
see today. A British
businessman started this company in a small house
which gradually expanded to  Or later, it was
acquired
by Gupta Brothers and the name of this company became
Bus Brothers but with time, there were
multiple changes in the ownership in this company
after which it changed and there
came a time in 1979 when Nabisco brand
which is known after one of the founders of Oreo,
if you know Oreo biscuits then it is a
brand of Nabisco,
they acquired this company, they used to own
a major stake of around 27-28% in
this company but the
existing promoter Wadia Group
acquired this company in around 1999,
so you can guess that
after the existing promoters, the share of this company is of more than 3 decades.
Apart from this, another interesting fact is
that when World War 2 happened, this
company was chosen as an official partner,
which the company used to
provide food biscuits to the soldiers, which was useful for
their future.  One
interesting fact is that
this company also supplied to the army during World War
II.